Hi, my name is Elliot.
This is how you can make a double barrel gun.
Okay, so what you're going to need is two straws, preferably the same kind.
And you're also going to need tape.
What you'll want to do first is take the two straws and try to align them about the same.
Next, what you want to do, put your finger on that place, take the tape and take a bit of tape.
Go back to where you aligned them, and try to tape them together.
It's important that you tape them up close to the end.
And you switch it to the other side.
Take a piece of tape, tear it off, and tape them together.
If it's too short, you can get more tape.
So what's so important about getting the tape at the end of the straws?
Well, let me tell you.
If you put the tape in the middle, then the ends of the straws can sway back and forth, and therefore you don't get as better aiming when you're shooting your straw.
So, make sure that you put the tape near the end and near the other end, okay?
Next what you want to do is chew two spit balls for the double cannon.
I have two in my mouth.
So, load the first one and load the second one in the other cannon.
It's getting a little tough.
Next, you aim and you shoot.
And let's see how this goes.
Wow, they're so close together.
That shows how accurate they can be.